[
    {
        "question": "I pick a star, for you to keep, The light is calm, give you protection, as a reminder of friends, also as ______ all challenges",
        "answer": "Answer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Being in your arms taught me what it means______ perfection of love",
        "answer": "Convenience"
    },
    {
        "question": "Love is space and time, not for a moment you have to want. Love needs a quiet space, to______ the heart",
        "answer": "speak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can't go on, Our world_____, If this is the end",
        "answer": "Different"
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm the one who keeps holding you tight, when you think______ turn away",
        "jawaban": "Mungkinkah"
    },
    {
        "soal": "Kau harus bisa berlapang dada. Kau harus bisa ambil______",
        "jawaban": "Hikmahnya"
    },
    {
        "soal": "Untuk apa? Untuk apa cinta tanpa_____, untuk apa cinta tanpa perbuatan. Tak ada artinya",
        "jawaban": "Kejujuran"
    },
    {
        "soal": "Ku bisa hadapi_____ terluka, yang pernah kurasa di waktu dulu",
        "jawaban": "Perihnya"
    },
    {
        "soal": "Ada yang lain, di senyummu, yang_____ lidahku gugup tak bergerak",
        "jawaban": "Membuat"
    },
    {
        "soal": "Aku sayang padamu, aku cinta padamu, semua kan ku_____ demi kebahagiaanmu",
        "jawaban": "Lakukan"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you miss this, it's still yours, ______ a question for you, how long should I wait for you",
        "answer": "I present"
    },
    {
        "question": "There is a space in my heart now you touch, I'm not falling _____ but I'm falling in love",
        "answer": "You are the most beautiful, which makes my heart calm, loving you will never be afraid, because you _____ everything I lack"
    },
    {
        "question": "I love you, I love you, only you in my heart, will never ______, until you become mine",
        "answer": "Replaced"
    },
    {
        "question": "I like her, maybe I love you, but _____ maybe, you'll be mine",
        "answer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "He he he is the love I've been waiting for waiting for, he he he he _____ my life",
        "answer": "Complete"
    },
    {
        "question": "Listen to my pain, this inner voice _____ your name, because half of me, you",
        "answer": "Call"
    },
    {
        "question": "Come on, sons of the nation, smell this country, ____ we are proud, Indonesia",
        "answer": "Make"
    },
    {
        "question": "Love, don't ever try _____ because here I need you",
        "answer": "Go"
    },
    {
        "question": "For what? What is love without _____, what is love without deeds",
        "answer": "Honesty"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you really have to separate, I will still be happy, if this is ______, you will still be in my soul",
        "answer": "The end"
    },
    {
        "question": "You know since the first time you met, you had a beautiful _____ in your eyes, you gave me a look of love",
        "answer": "Smile"
    },
    {
        "question": "You and I were created by time, just to love each other, maybe _____ together, knit love make love",
        "answer": "Destiny"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's wrong with this song, why do I _____ remember you, like I can feel your heartbeat and footsteps",
        "answer": "Back"
    },
    {
        "question": "I am a piece of your past story, who ____ wants to know how you are",
        "answer": "Just"
    },
    {
        "question": "Maybe someday, you'll be happy even though you're not with me",
        "answer": "Find"
    },
    {
        "question": "You are the one I want, even though I don't____, you are the one I imagine, the one I've always dreamed of",
        "answer": "Reveal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Too sweet to forget, good memories _____ just a dream",
        "answer": "With you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the neighbor's blanket, warm _____ in the cold, the nights are long, every time I sleep is always lonely",
        "answer": "My body"
    },
    {
        "question": "And it happened again, the old story that _____ returned, you were hurt again, from a complicated love you lived",
        "answer": "Repeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "The eagle in my chest, the eagle of my pride, I believe today will win, ignite ______, show your will, I believe today will win",
        "answer": "Your spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Until now, I feel ______ here, a feeling that will not fade with time",
        "answer": "survive"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can't _____, if you weren't here, I can't stop thinking, if you weren't with me anymore",
        "answer": "Imagine"
    },
    {
        "question": "There's a rainbow, in your eyeballs, and _____ yourself to say I love you",
        "answer": "Forcing"
    },
    {
        "question": "At least I've struggled, even though it's never priceless in your eyes, at least I've been waiting, _____ against my lonely heart",
        "answer": "Spray"
    },
    {
        "question": "Take me inside, into your warm, let me _____ dance in your arms",
        "answer": "There"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did you go, why did you leave, when I started loving you, wishing you were ____ in my heart, instead you went far from my life",
        "answer": "Love"
    },
    {
        "question": "Totally Iuu, want to hug youuuu, _____ hopeful, to love you",
        "answer": "hug"
    },
    {
        "question": "If we can't be together forever, should _____ be here, and if we can be together forever, I'll keep this love",
        "answer": "Waiting for you"
    }
]
